http://www.indyarts.org/privacy-policy

Sign-up for Newsletter
Any Given Child Indy (IPS K-8)
Sign-up for Newsletter
Any Given Child Indy (IPS K-8)
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy The Arts Council of Indianapolis respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. The Arts Council protects your online information in the same way it protects its information obtained through telephone and in-person transactions. Protecting the information you provide the Arts Council during a visit to the Council’s website (indyarts.org) is something that the Arts Council takes very seriously. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the Arts Council of Indianapolis collects, uses, maintains, and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the indyarts.org website ("Site"). By using this website, you are accepting the privacy practices set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Personal Identification InformationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, subscribe to our e-newsletters, make a donation, and in connection with other activities, services, features, or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-Personal Identification InformationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet Service Provider utilized or other similar information.
Web Browser CookiesOur Site may automatically assign "cookies" to enhance User experience. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.  By rejecting cookies, this could negatively affect the User’s ability to complete transactions or view areas within the Site.
How We Use Collected InformationThe Arts Council of Indianapolis may collect and use personal information to fulfill the User’s request for goods and services, including:Customer service and website improvementSending event invitationsPayment or donation processingSending newsletters through emailWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include organization news, updates, related product or service information. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How We Protect Your InformationWe have implemented a variety of procedures to protect information stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. We also maintain procedural safeguards that restrict access to your personal information to employees or agents who need to know your personal information in order to provide the products and services that are requested.
Sharing Your Personal InformationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third Party WebsitesUsers may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes To This Privacy PolicyThe Arts Council of Indianapolis has the discretion to modify or amend this privacy policy at any time, without notice. We encourage Users to read this policy each time you use the website to stay up-to-date and informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance Of These TermsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:
Arts Council of Indianapolisindyarts.org924 N Pennsylvania StreetIndianapolis IN 46204(317) 631-3301This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Joomla SEF URLs by Artio
Thank you to our funders
Visit Us
924 N Pennsylvania St Indianapolis, IN 46204
Arts Council of Indianapolis
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. 317.631.3301 Privacy Policy
Office Hours
Monday – Friday 9 am – 5 pm Saturday/Sunday Closed
Gallery 924 Hours
Open by appointment
